African-American related sheet music, and sheet music written by African-Americans, 1851-1974 M1433
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series II: Sheet Music with African-American themes
  - Ain't It De Truth?; Jamaica, Harold Arlen, E. Y. Harburg, 1957 (Flat-box 4, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Ain't Dat a Shame, John Queen, Walter Wilson, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Ain't Dat a Shame, John Queen, Walter Wilson, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Ain't You Coming Back to Dixieland, Raymond Egan, Richard Whiting, 1917 (Flat-box 4, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Alabama Shuffle, Joseph Ott, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Al Bernard's Complete Minstrel Folio, Al Bernard, 1935 (Flat-box 4, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Alexander, Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Alexander's Got a Jazz Band Now, Bud DeSylva, Chris Schonberg, 1917 (Flat-box 4, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Alimony Go' Way, C.E. Howell, R.E. Long, 1911 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Al Jolson Album of Songs, various, no date (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - All Among the Roses, Wm. Delehanty, arr. Carl Hess, 1872 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Alley Cat Song, The, Jack Harlen, Frank Bjorn, 1962 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Ambolena Snow, Lester Bodine, Geo. Maywood, 1896 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Amor, Gabriel Ruiz, Sunny Skylar, Ricardo Lopez Mendez, 1943 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Any Rags, Thos S. Allen, 1902 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - Anything Is Nice If It Comes From Dixieland, Grant Clarke, Geo. W. Meyer, Milton Ager, 1919 (Flat-box 4, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - At a Georgia Campmeeting, Kerry Mills, 1897 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - At an Ole Virginia Wedding, Maurice J. Steinberg, 1899 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - At the Coffee Cooler's Tea, Alex Sullivan, Harry De Costa, 1918 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - At Uncle Tom's Cabin Door, Chas. Bayha, Rubey Cowan, 1912 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Aunt Jemima's Picnic Day, J. Will Callahan, F. Henri Klickmann, 1914 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Aunt Jemima's Plaster, M.A.I., 18?? (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Aunty Skinner's Chicken Dinner, Arthur Fields, Earl Carroll, Theodore Morse, 1915 (Flat-box 4, Folder 4, Item 7)
  - Babau!, Georg Marcel, no date (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Babylon is Fallen, Henry C. Work, 1863 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Back, Back, Back to Baltimore, Harry Williams, Egbert Van Alstyne, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Back To Life, Chas. Hunter, 1905 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Beautiful, Eddie Leonard, Grace Stern, Jack Stern, 1929 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Because the Fortune Teller Told Me, Howard Emerson, Maurice J. Steinberg, 1900 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Bedelia, William Jerome, Hean Schwartz, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Belle of Honolulu, The, Lee Johnson, 1898 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Between the Devil And the Deep Blue Sea; Rhythm Mania, Ted Koehler, Harold Arlen, 1931 (Flat-box 4, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - Big Brown Booloo Eyes, Eddie Leonard, 1908 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Bill Bailey, Won't You Please Come Home?, Hughie Cannon, 1902 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Birmingham Papa, Al Bernard, 1924 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Black America, Harry H. Zickel, 1895 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Black Bottom, Ray Henderson, arr. Otto Lindemann, Otto Stransky, Fritz Rotter, 1927 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Black Bottom; George White's Scandals, Ray Henderson, B.G. DeSylva, Lew Brown, 1926 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - Black Cupid's Birthday, Seneca G. Lewis, 1898 (Flat-box 4, Folder 6, Item 7)
  - Black Feather, Irene M. Giblin-O'Brien, 1908 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Boatman's Dance, 18?? (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Boston Banjo Band, M.C. Ives, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Buckwheat Cakes, Fred Sloop, Tell Taylor, 1911 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Bullfrog and the Coon, The, Felix Feist, Jos. S. Nathan, 1906 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Buy a Bale of Cotton For Me, L. Wolfe Gilbert, Lewis F. Muire, 1914 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - By the Light of the Jungle Moon, Powell I. Ford, J.C. Atkinson, 1911 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - By the Watermelon Vine Lindy Lou, Thos. S. Allen, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - Canoe Song, Arthur Wimperis, Mischa Spolianksy, 1935 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Can't Help Lovin' Dat Man; Show Boat, Oscar Hammerstein II, Jerome Kern, 1927 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Can't Yo' Heah Me Callin' Caroline, Wm. H. Gardner, Caro Roma, 1914 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Carolina Mammy, Billy James, 1922 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - Chain of Fools, Don Covay, 1967 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - Chicken Charlie, Ashley Ballou, 1905 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - Chocolate Soldier From the U.S.A., Elton Box, Sonny Cox, Lewis Ilda, 1944 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - Chuckles, Frank C. Keithley, 1906 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 8)
  - Cindy, I Dreams About You, Dave Reed Jr., 1900 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 9)
  - Coal Black Mammy, Laddie Cliff, Ivy St. Helier, 1921 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 10)
  - Cocoanut Dance, Andrew Herman, 1891 (Flat-box 4, Folder 8, Item 11)
  - Colored Major, The, S.R. Henry, 1900 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Colored Ragamuffins, The, S.R. Henry, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Come Along Mandy, Nora Bayes, Jack Norworth, 1910 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - Come Back Mirandy, Maurice Harnett, James Byrnes, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - Coon Band Contest, A, Arthur Pryor, 1899 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - Coon Banshee, The, Glen Mac Donough, Victor Herbert, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 6)
  - Coon! Coon! Coon!, Gene Jefferson, Leo Friedman, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 7)
  - Coon! Coon! Coon!, Gene Jefferson, Leo Friedman, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 9, Item 8)
  - Coon's Eye, The, Walter Stearns, 1899 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Coons in the Canebrake, M.S. Calyson, 1900 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Coon's March, J. Ed. Lakeman, 1893 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Coontown Chimes, Harry S. Webster, 1902 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Coon Town's Vacation, Chas. Brown, 1900 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Copper Colored Gal; 27th Edition Cotton Club Parade, Benny Davis, J. Fred Coots, 1936 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - Cotton Bolls, Chas. Hunter, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 10, Item 7)
  - Cotton Field Dance, Monroe H. Rosenfeld, 1892 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Cotton Field Dance, Al. W. Brown, 1904 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Cotton Pickers, The, Chas. S. TarBox, 1899 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Crab Apples, Percey Wenrich, 1908 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 4)
  - Creole Belles, J. Bodewalt Lampe, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Dancing with Ma Baby, Bert. R. Anthony, 1902 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 6)
  - Dandy Darkies, Roger Bernard, 1909 (Flat-box 4, Folder 11, Item 7)
  - Darkey's Wedding March, B.A. Koellhoffer, arr. Arthur H. Weberbauer, 1912 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Darkies Mardi Gras, The, Theodore Wenzlik, 1906 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Darktown Colored Band, The, Harry S. Miller, 1896 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Dar's a Meeting Here to Night, Pete Devonear, 1875 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 4)
  - Dat Lovin' Rag, Victor H. Smalley, Bernard Adler, 1907 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 5)
  - Dat Man's All Mine, J. A. LeBarge, 1899 (Flat-box 4, Folder 12, Item 6)
  - Deacon Jones, Johnny Lange, Hy Heath, Richard Loring, 1943 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - De Five Senses, John Golden, Raymond Hubbell, 1934 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - De Gospel Bells Am Sounding, George W. Majors, 1885 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - De Little Cabins All am Empty Now, Thos. P. Westendorf, 1881 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - De Old Folks Waiting, B.E. Lucian, Brother Gardner, 1890 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 5)
  - Don't Be a Baby, Baby, Buddy Kaye, Howard Steiner, 1946 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 6)
  - Don't Let Nobody Steal You From Me!, R.P. Weston, Bert Lee, Harris Weston, 1926 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 7)
  - Don't Make Dem Scandalous Eyes At Me, Lee Johnson, 1902 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 8)
  - Don't Misunderstand; Shaft's Big Score, Gordon Parks, 1972 (Flat-box 4, Folder 13, Item 9)
  - Don't Worry 'Bout Me, Cotton Club Parade, Ted Koehler, Rube Bloom, 1939 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Down and Out Blues, W. Earthman Farrell, Arthur Sizemore, 1925 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Down on the Ohio, Edith Kingsley, 1896 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Do Your Duty Doctor!, Irving Berlin, Ted Snyder, 1909 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 4)
  - Eat, Drink and be Merry, George R. Wilson, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 5)
  - Educated Coon is Best of All, An, Scott Lawrence, 1901 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 6)
  - Egypt, Clare Kummer, 1903 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 7)
  - Eli Green's Cake Walk, Sadie Koninsky, arr. Chas. E. Pratt, 1898 (Flat-box 4, Folder 14, Item 8)
  - Emmalina, Bert Potter, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Enjoy Yourselves, Dave Reed Jr., Chas B. Ward, 1897 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Entrada Libre, Rondolfo Sasson, Luis Teisseire (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Espanharlem, William J. Reddick, 1938 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Eva's Parting, Miss Mary A. Collier, F. James, 1852 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Ev'ry Darkey Had a Raglan On, Brown and Allen, 1901 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Exodus, Carlos V. Cusachs, 1914 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Farewell Mister Abner Hemingway, Wm. Jerome, Jean Schwartz, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Fashion Rag, Chas. Cohen, 1912 (Flat-box 5, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Fi Hi Hi (the Black Shakers Song and Polka), Even Horn (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Floating Down the River on the Alabam, Lew Brown, Albert Von Tilzer, 1913 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Four Little Blackberries, Lawrence B. O'Connor, 1907 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Foxy Sam, John F. Barth, 1903 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Friend of Mind Told a Friend of Mine, Alfred Bryan, Kendis and Paley, 1906 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Gang That Sang "Heart Of My Heart", The, Ben Ryan, 1946 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Gib Me Dat Watermillion, Thos. P. Westendorf, 1882 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Give Cinda the Cake, George Graham, Theo. A. Metz, 1898 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Going from de Cotton Fields, Thos. P. Westendorf, 1879 (Flat-box 5, Folder 2, Item 9)
  - Good-Bye Boys, Andrew B. Sterling, Wm. Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer, 1913 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Good-Bye Mister Greenback, Thos. S. Allen, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Good Morning Carrie, Eustasio Rosales, 1901 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Good Old Jeff, G. W. H. Griffin Esq., 1853 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Great Pretender, The, Buck Ram, 1955 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Have You Seen My Henry Brown?, Dave J. Clark, Albert Von Tilzer, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Headin' Your Way, Larry Yoell, Otto Cesana, 1925 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - He Cert'ny was Good to Me, Jean C. Havez, A.B. Sloane, 1898 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - Hee-Haw, Ol' Fool Mule, Tad James, 1934 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 9)
  - Hey There! My Sadie, Andrew B. Sterling, Bartley C. Costello, 1900 (Flat-box 5, Folder 3, Item 10)
  - High Hat, a Piccolo and a Cane, A, Lew Brown, Sammy Fain, Harry Akst, 1936 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - High Yellow Cake Walk, F. Henri Klickmann, 1916 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Honey Does You Love Yer Man?, Walter H. Ford, John W. Bratton, 1895 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Honey, O!, Percy Gaunt, 1894 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Honkey Tonk, John Raymond Hubbell, 1899 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Hot Tamale Alley, May Irwin, Geo. M. Cohan, 1896 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - How Could Red Riding Hood?, A.P. Randolph, arr. R.D. Whichard, 1926 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 7)
  - Huckleberry Finn Cake Walk, H.S. Brennan, 1924 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Hush-a-Bye, Frank X. Galvin, Robert E. Spencer, 1926 (Flat-box 5, Folder 4, Item 9)
  - Hush, Little Baby, Don't You Cry!, F. Belasco (Monroe H. Rosenfeld), 1884 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - I Ain't Doin' No Good No How, Fred E. Colip, 1946 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - I Ain't Got No Use for Sleep, Ralph Bicknell, 1903 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Ida! Sweet as Apple Cider, Eddie Leonard, 1932 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - I Don't Care If Yo' Nebber Comes Back, Raymond A. Brown, Monroe H. Rosenfeld, 1897 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - I Don't Know How to Tell Yer How I Lubs Yer, Bennett Scott, 1897 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - I Don't Know Where I'm Goin' But I'm on My Way, Joe Bren, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - I Don't Want No Imitation Man, Fred J. Hamill, Percy Wenrich, 1907 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - I Feel Religion Comin on, Marguerite A. Robinson, J. Russel Robinson, 1910 (Flat-box 5, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - I Got Plenty o' Nuttin'; Porgy And Bess, Ira Gershwin, DuBose Heyward, George Gershwin, 1935 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - I Hates to Get Up Early in De Morn, John Queen, Hughie Cannon, 1901 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - I Haven't Mentioned Mammy, Ray Sherwood, Marion Short, 1926 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - I Just Couldn't Take it Baby; Lew Leslie's Blackbirds of 1934, Mann Hoiner, Albert Nichols, 1933 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - I'll be Back in a Minute, But I Got to Go Now, Herbert Ingraham, 1906 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - I'll be Waiting Lady Mine, Harry Lewis Rogers, 1902 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - I Long to Hear the Darkies Sing!, Rolla Broadwell, 1905 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 7)
  - I'm Alabama Bound, John J. Puderer, Robt. Hoffman, 1914 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 8)
  - I'm Always in the Mood for You; 3rd Edition of the Cotton Club Parade, Benny Davis, J. Fred Coots, 1937 (Flat-box 5, Folder 6, Item 9)
  - I'm Awfully Strong for You, Geo. M. Cohan, 1908 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - I'm Going Back to Birmingham, J. Will Callahan, Paul Pratt, 1913 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - I'm Going Back to Dixie Land, Jessie Sidnam O'Reilly, Pat O'Reilly, 1925 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - I'm Gonna Jazz My Way Right Straight Thru Paradise, Will E. Skidmore, Marshall Walker, 1919 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - I'm Gonna Rise, Richard M. Gunn, 1931 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - I'm Looking for an Argument!, Porcelain and Berg, Maurice Porcelain, 1904 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - I'm Looking for the Sheik of Araby, Art Noel, Don Hart, Lewis Ilda, 1938 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Impecunious Davis, Kerry Mills, 1899 (Flat-box 5, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - In My Dream of Dixieland, Tad James, 1933 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - In My Little Hope Chest; Honey, W. Frank Harling, Sam Coslow, 1930 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - I'se Gwine to de Shuckin Of de Corn, Ernest DeLancey Pierson, Chas. Lande, 1881 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - I'se Gwine to Highball, C.C. Cocroft, N. Weldon Cocroft, 1910 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - It's Nobody's Business but My Own, Will E. Skidmore, Marshall Walker, 1919 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - It Takes a Long Tall Brown-Skin Gal to Make a Preacher Lay His Bible Down, Marshall Walker, Will E. Skidmore, 1917 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - It Won't be Very Long, Estelle Baker, 1898 (Flat-box 5, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - I've Got a Feelin' for You, Edward Madden, Theodore Morse, 1904 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - I've Got a White Man Running My Automobile, Harry Zaun, Halsey K. Mohr, 1906 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - I've Got the Ol' Virginny Pickaninny Blues, Joe McKiernan, 1924 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - I've Got to Dance Till the Band Gits Through, G.A. Spink, 1906 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - I've Said My Last Farewell, Ed Rose, Fred Fischer, 1906 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - I Want Dem Presents Back, Paul West, 1896 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 6)
  - I Want My Lulu, Lew Dockstader, Karl St. Clair, 1897 (Flat-box 5, Folder 9, Item 7)
  - I Want My Mammy, Geo. B. Wehner, Louis Breau, 1921 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - I Want Someone to be Real Nice to Me, W.A. Thomas, 1908 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - I Wants to be the Leadin' Lady, George Totten Smith, Harry Von Tilzer, 1901 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - I Want yer Ma Honey, Fay Templeton, 1895 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Jamaican Rumba, Arthurt Benjamin, arr. Joan Trimble, 1938 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Jigadeer Johnson, Seneca G. Lewis, 1918 (Flat-box 5, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - Jolly Jingles Rag, F.H. Losey, 1913 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - June Moon, Earl J. Benham, Wm. J. Vanderveer, 1907 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Jungle Caravan, Miltona Moore, 1942 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Just Because She Made Dem Goo-Goo Eyes, John Queen, Hughey Cannon, 1900 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 4)
  - Just Kiss Yourself Good-Bye, Wm. Jerome, Jean Schwartz, 1902 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Keemo, Kimo!, unknown, n.d. (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 6)
  - Kentucky Babe, Richard Henry Buck, Adam Geibel, 1896 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 7)
  - Kentucky Babe, Arthur C. Liscombe, 1922 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 8)
  - Kinky Kids Parade, Gus Kahn, Walter Donaldson, 1925 (Flat-box 5, Folder 11, Item 9)
  - Laugh! Oh, Coons!, J.W. Wheeler, 1891 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Lawd, You Made the Night too Long, Sam. M. Lewis, Victor Young, 1932 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Legalize My Name; St. Louis Woman, Harold Arlen, Johnny Mercer, 1946 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Legend of Lady Day, Louis McKay, Curtis R. Lewis, 1969 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 4)
  - Little Alabama Coon, Hattie Starr, 1898 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 5)
  - Little Black Me, Thurland Chattaway, 1914 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 6)
  - Little Eva, John G. Whittier, Manuel Emilio, 1852 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 7)
  - Little More Cider, A, Austin Hart, 1853 (Flat-box 5, Folder 12, Item 8)
  - Love Letters, Edward Heyman, Victor Young, 1945 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Love! Love! Love!, Teddy McRae, Sid Wyche, Sunny David, 1956 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Lucinda Cinda Jane, Joseph Hart, 1894 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - Lucy Neal, W.M.T., 18?? (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - Ma!, Sidney Clare, Con Conrad, 1921 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 5)
  - Ma Ebony Belle, Ed Gardenier, Maurice Levi, 1901 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 6)
  - Magic Touch, The, Buck Ram, 1956 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 7)
  - Mah High Steppin' Lady, Sam Newland, Fred Brown, 1899 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 8)
  - Make a Fuss over Me, Edward Madden, Theodore Morse, 1904 (Flat-box 5, Folder 13, Item 9)
  - Make Me Your Baby, Roger Atkins, Helen Miller, 1965 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Ma Lady Lu, Chas. W. Doty, Edwin S. Brill, 1899 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Mammy's Carolina Twins, Lee Johnson, 1899 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Mammy's Little Carolina Coons, R.C. Young, E.S.S. Huntington, 1917 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 4)
  - Mammy's Little Coal Black Rose, Raymond Egan, Richard A. Whiting, 1916 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 5)
  - Mammy's Little Kinky Headed Boy, Joseph M. White, George J. Trinkaus, 1926 (Flat-box 5, Folder 14, Item 6)
  - Mammy's Lullaby, John L. Herman, 1918 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Mammy's Lullaby, Lee S. Roberts, J. Will Callahan, 1918 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Mammy's Shufflin' Dance, L. Wolfe Gilbert, Melville J. Gideon, 1918 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Mandy Lane, Wm. McKenna, 1908 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Mandy Lee, Thurland Chattaway, 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Mandy Loves Me, Edwin M. Royle, Martha Ryole, 1903 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Mandy Make up Your Mind; Dixie to Broadway, Grant Clarke, Roy Turk, Geo. W. Meyer, Arthur Johnston, 1924 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Man with the Jingle, The, Wm. B. Friedlander, Chas. E. Mullen, 1905 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Ma Pickaninny Babe, Chas. L. Johnson, 1913 (Flat-box 6, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Massa's in the Cold, Cold Ground Trans., Carl Wilhelm Kern, 1903 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Ma Starlight Sue, Wm. Gould, 1901 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Ma Tiger Lily, Clay M. Greene, A.B. Sloane, 1900 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Melon Time in Dixieland, Dave Ringle, 1921 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Mid the Fields of Snowy Cotton, Otto Heinzman, John Heinzman, 1906 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Minstrel's March Two-Step, Al. J. Whyte, 1913 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Minstrel Show Parade, The, W.R. Williams, 1913 (Flat-box 6, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Mississippi Side-Step, Leo. E. Berliner, 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Moon, Moon, Nat D. Mann, 1901 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Moonlight in Jungleland, Dempsey and Schmid, 1909 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Mormon Coon, The, Raymond A. Browne, Henry Clay Smith, 1905 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Moving Day, Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, 1906 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Much Obliged to You, Benjamin Hapgood Burt, 1907 (Flat-box 6, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - My Ann Elizer, Malcolm Williams, 1898 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - My Baby Just Cares for Me, Gus Kahn, Walter Donaldson, no date (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - My Charcoal Charmer, Will D. Cobb, Gus Edwards, 1900 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - My Charcoal Charmer, Will D. Cobb, Gus Edwards, 1900 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - My Creole Lady, Chas. E. Washburn, Edw. J. McDermott, 1902 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - My Gal is a High-Born Lady, Barney Fagan, 1896 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - My Hannah Lady, Whose Black Baby Is You?, Dave Reed, Jr., 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - My Honolulu Lady, Lee Johnson, 1898 (Flat-box 6, Folder 4, Item 7)
  - My Lady Hottentot March and Two Step, Wm. Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer, 1901 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - My Little Creole Babe, Maude Nugent, 1903 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - My Name is Morgan but It Ain't J.P., Will A. Mahoney, Halsey K. Mohr, 1906 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - My Octoroon Lady, Oscar F.G. Day, E.F. Geo. Koehler, 1903 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - My Old Kentucky Home, Stephen C. Foster, 1853 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - My Old Kentucky Home, Stephen C. Foster, 1896 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - My South Carolina Lil, Lee Austin, 1901 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - My Sunflower Sue, Walter H. Ford, John W. Bratton, 1900 (Flat-box 6, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Navajo, Harry Williams, Egbert Van Alstyne, 1904 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Necerstandchen [A Coon Band Contest], Arthur Pryor, 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Negro Oddities, arr. George Schleiffarth, 1882 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Never My Love, Don Addrisi, Dick Addrisi, 1967 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Nigger Blues, Le Roy Lasses White, 1913 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Night Lights, Sammy Gallop, Chester Conn, 1956 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - Nothin' from Nothin' Leaves You, Rose and Snyder, 1905 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 7)
  - Oh Boys Carry Me 'Long, Stephen C. Foster, 1851 (Flat-box 6, Folder 6, Item 8)
  - Oh Henry! Mammy Surely Paddled Me, Harold Dixon, 1919 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Oh! I Wishes I Could See My Little Cabin, Shell F. Acree, Will Earhart, 1897 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 2)